xfactorindonesia.com 2015-06-15

# FremantleMedia Asia

## Data Protection Statement

This Privacy Policy explains the data collection and use practices, which is operated by FremantleMedia. By using this site, you signify your assent to our Privacy Policy.   
We are committed to protecting your privacy and honouring the integrity of your personal information. We do not sell any information collected through this site to others except as disclosed in this Privacy Policy. If you have any requests concerning your personal information or any queries with regard to these practices please contact our Privacy Officer by e-mail at [privacy.officer@fremantlemedia.co.id](mailto:privacy.officer@fremantlemedia.co.id).

## Personal Information

We collect personal information from you when you (i) submit questions or material to us, (ii) register on this site, (iii) purchase a product from us, (iv) e-mail us or (v) enter one of our contests or sweepstakes.   
We use such personal information collected through this site for the purposes of:

  * providing a personalised service
  * conducting market research surveys
  * fulfilling product orders
  * running features that incorporate submissions to the site
  * running sweepstakes and contests and
  * providing you with information about, and access to, products and services we offer, either ourselves or jointly with or on behalf of other organisations.

If you do not wish to receive information about our products or services, or the products or services offered jointly with or on behalf of other organisations, please check the appropriate box on the registration page, sweepstakes/contests page or other relevant form or page through which the information is collected. Please note that by using any free e-mail account we may offer through this site, you may receive occasional communications from selected third party sponsors and partners. If you do not wish to receive such communications, you should not use the free e-mail service.

## Non-Personal Information

We collect information in the aggregate form through the use of cookies and IP addresses, such as demographic information and browsing patterns. Such information does not identify any individual and will not be linked any personal information. We use such information to:

  * build up marketing profiles
  * aid strategic development
  * manage our relationship with advertisers and
  * audit usage of the site.

We may share such information, in the aggregate form only, with our affiliates, partners or advertisers, or other third parties.

## Use of Cookies

We use "cookies" to identify you when you visit this site and to build up a demographic profile. Our use of cookies also allows registered users to be presented with a personalised version of the site.  
A cookie is a small piece of information sent by a web server to a web browser, which enables the server to collect information back from the browser. Find out more about the use of cookies on [http://www.cookiecentral.com](http://www.cookiecentral.com/)

## Submissions

Any personal information you choose to provide to us with your submissions posted to this site may appear on the site, but only to identify you as the author of the submission, unless you expressly authorise us to make further use of the information on the site.

## Chat Areas/Bulletin Boards

If you voluntarily disclose personal information on the bulletin boards or in the chat areas on this site, that information can also be collected and used by others and may result in unsolicited messages from other people.

## Privacy Policy for Children Under 13

In accordance with the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act (commonly referred to as COPPA), we do not require children under the age of 13 to provide us with any more information than is reasonably necessary to participate and make use of this site and under no circumstances do we require children under the age of 13 to provide us with any personal information. Children under the age of 13 should not submit or post any personal information without the written consent of their parents or legal guardians. If you are a child under the age of 13 and want to submit your personal information to us, you should ask your parents to send an e-mail to [privacy.officer@fremantlemedia.co.id](mailto:privacy.officer@fremantlemedia.co.id). specifically allowing us to collect your personal information through this site. By doing so, you allow us to alert your parent or guardian about this site's Privacy Policy. We do not intend to sell, license or trade any such information collected to third parties. Parents may review or change the personal information of their children provided to us or further refuse our collection of such information by sending an e-mail to [privacy.officer@fremantlemedia.co.id](mailto:privacy.officer@fremantlemedia.co.id).

## Partner Sites / Linked Sites

Our site features several activities, which are co-sponsored or operated by other sites. These activities will be identifiable by their co-branding. While these activities originate on this site, they may link to other sites not operated by FremantleMedia. We have no control over the privacy practices or the content of any of our co-sponsors and strongly recommend that you check their privacy policies before engaging in these activities. Additionally, our site contains links to other sites, including those of advertisers. We have no control over the privacy practices of advertisers or other sites to which we provide links from this site. For example, if you click on a banner advertisement, the click takes you off this site. These other sites may use cookies, collect data or solicit personal information. We strongly recommend that you check the applicable privacy policy of the site to which you are linking.

## Security of Information

We take precautions to ensure the security of personal information submitted by users. Unfortunately, no electronic communication over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. While we strive to take care to protect your personal information, FremantleMedia cannot warrant the security of any information that you submit to us, and you do so at your own risk. We do offer secured-server transactions that encrypt your information in transit to thwart someone from intercepting it and misusing it when collecting credit card information for online purchases. We also store any personal information, including credit card numbers, in a secure area to which the general public does not have access.

## Updating Personal Information

If you would like to change any contact or billing information, or if you no longer desire to receive any marketing communications from us or our partners, please email us at [privacy.officer@fremantlemedia.co.id](mailto:privacy.officer@fremantlemedia.co.id).

## Changes in Privacy Policy

We reserve the right to change this policy at any time, and will post any changes to this policy as soon as they go into effect without prior notice to you. Any such changes are effective as of the date such changes are posted on this page. Please check this page periodically to view our most current Privacy Policy.
